aniview.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Aniview

### Introduction

Aniview Inc. and Aniview Ltd. (collectively “ **Aniview** “, “ **Company** “, “ **we** ” or “ **us** “) executes agreements with its publishers (“ **Publishers** “), under which the Publishers receive access to Aniview’s digital marketplace, AdServer or AVPlayer (collectively, the “ **Services** “), allowing such Publishers to deliver video content and display video ads on the Publisher’s online properties (the “ **Properties** “).

This Privacy Policy provides information regarding Aniview’s privacy practices, including details with respect to the information that may be collected about end users that visit the Properties that embed our Services (“ **you** “, “ **your** ” or “ **End-User** “).

In this Privacy Policy, you can learn about:

  * **WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**
  * **MINORS**
  * **HOW WE USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION?**
  * **MARKETING**
  * **WITH WHOM WE SHARE INFORMATION?**
  * **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**
  * **THIRD PARTY TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**
  * **THIRD PARTY SERVICES**
  * **RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**
  * **YOUR RIGHTS**
  * **HOW WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SECURED**
  * **CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**
  * **HOW TO CONTACT US**

### WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

We collect the following categories of information in connection with our Services:

  * **_Personal Information_** **–** the first type of information we collect is information that identifies or may identify you with reasonable means (hereinafter “ **Personal Information** “), including **:**
  * **_Device and app information_** – this category includes your device’s type and model, system language, the device’s operating system (such as Android or iOS), carrier name, browsers installed on the device (such as Chrome or Safari), your device’s IP address, and identifiers assigned to your device, such as its iOS Identifier for Advertising (IDFA), Android Advertising ID, or other types of unique device identifiers (a number uniquely allocated to your device by your device manufacturer).

  * **_Non-Personal Information_** **–** the second type of information we collect is un-identified and non-identifiable information pertaining to an End-Users, which may be made available or gathered via the End-User’s use of the Services (“ **Non-Personal Information** ”). Non-Personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information and aggregated usage information, and may contain, among other things, the User’s operating system, type of browser, screen resolution, browser and keyboard language, the User’s ‘click-stream’ and activities on the Services, the period of time the User visited the Services and related time stamps, etc. **For avoidance of doubt, any Non-personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists**.

Types of Non-personal Information we collect from or about you:

  * **_Ad information_** – this category includes information about the online ads and personalized content we have served (or attempted to serve) to you. It includes how many times an ad has been served to you, what page the ad appeared on, whether you viewed, clicked on or otherwise interacted with the ad, ad engagement history and whether you visited the advertiser’s website, downloaded an app or purchased the product or service advertised.
  * **_Location information_** – the Company collects information about your coarse location (such as city and country). For example, we may use the IP address to identify your general location. This information does not tell us where your device is precisely located. This information is sent as a normal part of internet traffic.
  * In addition, certain advertisers may also collect the precise location of your device (using GPS signals, device sensors, Wi-Fi access points, Bluetooth signals, Beacons signals and cell tower ids that can be used to derive or estimate precise location, or other geo-location data), when location services have been enabled by the End-User (you typically have to choose to turn on device-based location services).
  * **_Technical and log information_** : In order to enhance the functionality of the Services and to provide you with a better user experience, we collect technical information transmitted by your device, including certain software and hardware information (e.g. the type of browser and operating system your device uses, language preference, access time and the domain name of the website from which you linked to the Services; etc.).
  * **_Analytics information_** : We collect information about your use of the Services, such as applications’ usage, log files, the End-User activity (e.g. pages viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, online browsing, clicks, actions, etc.), time stamps, alerts, etc. This information is collected for amongst other things troubleshooting errors and bugs as well as for research and analytics purposes about your use of the Services.
  * **Anonymous information** : We may anonymize or de-identify the information collected by the Services or via other means so that the information cannot, on its own, personally identify you. Our use and disclosure of such aggregated or de-identified information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to others without limitation and for any purpose, such as for advertising or marketing purposes.

### MINORS

The Services are not designed or directed to persons under the age of 16 or persons under the age of legal consent with respect to the use of the Services of any jurisdiction, whichever is higher (“ **Legally of Age** ”). If you are not Legally of Age, you should not download or use the Services nor provide any Personal Information to us.

We reserve the right to access and verify any Personal Information collected from you. In the event that we become aware that a user who is not Legally of Age has shared any information, we may discard such information. If you have any reason to believe that a minor has shared any information with us, please contact us through the contact details available below.

### HOW WE USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION?

We use your Personal Information for the purposes listed below:

  * **Serving ads** – allow our Publishers to promote advertising, apps and content in their Properties, and to allow advertisers to bid on Publishers’ inventory.
  * **Serve interest-based advertising and personalized content** – enable our partners to infer interests and serve ads and personalized content to End-Users based on their behavior, app activity and inferred interests.
  * **Ad reporting and conversions** – measure ad performance, report to advertisers when and how End-Users have viewed or clicked on their ads, or visited their website, and to report to Publishers when and how ads were shown on their properties and were clicked on.
  * **Analytics and frequency capping** – allow our Publishers to analyze their applications (for this purpose, we use aggregated and anonymous benchmark data) and prevent End-Users from seeing the same ad too many times.
  * **Fraud detection and prevention  **– identify invalid or incentivized clicks (or ad queries) and protect us and our partners from fraudulent behavior.
  * **Providing and improving our Services** – audit, research and analyze information in order to maintain, protect, and improve our services and develop new services, and to ensure that our technologies function properly.
  * Enforce our policies, resolve disputes and communicate with you.

### WITH WHOM WE SHARE INFORMATION?

We do not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information with third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. The Personal Information will be disclosed to Recipients only to the extent required for the specific purpose, as stipulated in this Privacy Policy.

We share Personal Information with any of the following recipients:

  * A Publisher whose Properties you have accessed to – we share information about how you have interacted with that Publisher’s Properties app its ads and personalized content.
  * An advertiser whose ad you interacted with – we share information about how you have interacted with that advertiser’s ads.
  * Subcontractors and third party service providers, as well as their subcontractors, which by way of example include (but is not limited to) cloud computing companies, marketing affiliates, fraud prevention services, and other data verifiers.
  * With our subsidiaries and related companies.
  * In connection with legal proceedings – when we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, our partners or any other third party.
  * In connection with a sale of our business – if a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets, we may disclose your information in connection with the sale.
  * In addition, we may disclose aggregated, anonymized information with other third parties. This information cannot be used to identify you.
  * Whenever we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or legal claims, enforce our policies (including our User Agreement and Privacy Policy), protect your safety or the safety of others, as well as to investigate or prevent any fraud, for security reasons or to help us with any other related technical issue.

### TRANSFER OF INFORMATION

Since we operate globally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Information to countries outside the European Union. The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union.

We use best efforts to ensure that your Personal Information is protected in accordance with our privacy policy, through contractual means (such as by using the contractual clauses approved by the relevant regulators for data transfer) or other means (such as ensuring that the jurisdiction imposes adequate safeguards for data protection).

### THIRD PARTY TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

When you visit or access our Services (for example when you visit our websites), we use (and authorize third parties to use) web beacons, cookies, pixels, scripts, tags and other technologies (“ **Tracking Technologies** “).

The Tracking Technologies allow us to automatically collect information about you and your online behavior, as well as your device (for example your computer or mobile device), for different purposes, such as in order to enhance your navigation on our Services, improve our Services’ performance and customize your experience on our Services. We also use this information to collect statistics about the usage of our Services, perform analytics, deliver content which is tailored to your interests and administer services to our End-Users, advertisers, publishers, customers and partners.

We also allow third parties to collect information about you through Tracking Technologies.

### THIRD PARTY SERVICES

While using the Services you may encounter links to third party websites, services or applications. Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible, downloadable, or otherwise distributed through the Services.

Please be advised that such third party websites, services or applications are independent from the Company. We assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such third party websites and/or services. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use of such third party websites and/or services, as their terms, not ours, will apply to any of your interactions with such third parties.

You should always review their privacy practices carefully before providing Personal Information to such third parties.

You are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risks of using any third-party websites, services or applications. You agree that we shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such third party sites and your usage of them.

### RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

While using the Services you may encounter links to third party websites, services or applications. Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any third party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible, downloadable, or otherwise distributed through the Services.

Please be advised that such third party websites, services or applications are independent from the Company. We assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such third party websites and/or services. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use of such third party websites and/or services, as their terms, not ours, will apply to any of your interactions with such third parties.

You should always review their privacy practices carefully before providing Personal Information to such third parties.

You are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risks of using any third-party websites, services or applications. You agree that we shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such third party sites and your usage of them.

### YOUR RIGHTS

If you reside in the EU or in another jurisdiction that affords you with the below rights, you may contact us at any time through the contact details available below, and request:

  1. To access or delete any Personal Information relating to you
  2. To change or update any Personal Information relating to you (for example, if you believe that your Personal Information is incorrect, you may ask to have it corrected or deleted). Note that you may also request that we will correct errors with regard to your Personal Information (except in cases where the information is required to be kept in its original format under any applicable laws and regulations);
  3. That we will restrict or cease any further use of your Personal Information;
  4. That we will provide the Personal Information you volunteered to us in a machine-readable format.

Please note that these rights are not absolute and requests are subject to any applicable legal requirements. We may also rectify, replenish or remove incomplete or inaccurate information, at any time and at our own discretion, in accordance with our internal policies.

### HOW WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SECURED

We take great care in implementing and maintaining the security of the Services and your information. We have put in place appropriate physical and technological safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect and store.

We employ industry standard procedures and controls to ensure the safety of our users’ information. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse the Services, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this Privacy Policy on the Services and/or we will send you an e-mail regarding such changes to the e-mail address that you volunteered. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on any of the above mentioned methods. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date, and your continued use of the Services after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any general questions about the Services or the information that we collect about you and how we use it, please contact us via email at [info@aniview.com](mailto:info@aniview.com) or by sending a letter to:

Aniview INC,

79 Madison Street

New York, NY

We will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe. Please feel free to reach out to us at any time. If you are unsatisfied with our response, you can reach out to the applicable data protection supervisory authority.
